

# **Aleix Esteve Gisbert**

Date of birth: 25/01/2000

Nationality: Spanish

## **CONTACT**

- Agustina d'Aragó 7243870 Amposta, Spain(Home)
- aleix.esteve.gisbert@gmail.co m
- (+34) 634440369
- https:// aleixestevegisbert.github.io/
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ aleix-estevegisbert-093916178/

#### **ABOUT MF**

I am an enthusiast of the IT highly motivated and passionate web developer with a solid foundation in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. Also worked with most of the pioneer web frameworks like Laravel, Django or Node.js. I have worked most of the time in group environments, where each member had a specific task to do.

I am a curious and always willing to learn something new every day.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**2017 - 2018** Amposta, Spain

Computer equipment operator BEEP INFORMATICA, AMPOSTA

• Informatic maintenance (of office computers, servers, videogame computers, routers, printers,...) both hardware and software.

**05/2019 - 06/2019** Amposta, Spain

- Web Developer SpeedSix Wheels
  - Development on the WordPress company website with JQuery, HTML, PHP, SQL.

2019 - 2022 Amposta, Spain

- **Production operator** GiGroup Spain ETT (Saica Pack)
  - Operator on the cardboard corrugating machine production line. (In summers)

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

09/2020 - 06/2023 Igualada, Spain

 Graduated in Digital Interaction Techniques and Computing Universitat de Lleida

2018 - 2020 Amposta, Spain

Higher Technician in Web Application Development IES Montsià

**09/2016 - 06/2018** Amposta, Spain

**Technician in microcomputer systems and networks** IES Montsia

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

**MOTHER TONGUE(S):** Catalan | Spanish

OTHER LANGUAGE(S): English B2